<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Computerize</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="definition">Flowchart is a graphical representation of an algorithm. Programmers often use it as a program-planning tool to solve a problem. It makes use of symbols which are connected among them to indicate the flow of information and processing.  <br /> <br /> The process of drawing a flowchart for an algorithm is known as “flowcharting”</string>
    <string name="gdg_description_terminal"><b>1. Terminal:</b> The oval symbol indicates Start, Stop and Halt in a program’s logic flow. A pause/halt is generally used in a program logic under some error conditions. Terminal is the first and last symbols in the flowchart.</string>
    <string name="input_output"><b>2. Input/Output:</b> A parallelogram denotes any function of input/output type. Program instructions that take input from input devices and display output on output devices are indicated with parallelogram in a flowchart. "</string>
    <string name="process"><b>3. Processing:</b> A box represents arithmetic instructions. All arithmetic processes such as adding, subtracting, multiplication and division are indicated by action or process symbol.</string>
    <string name="decision"><b>4. Decision:</b> Diamond symbol represents a decision point. Decision based operations such as yes/no question or true/false are indicated by diamond in flowchart. "</string>
    <string name="connectors"><b>5. Connectors:</b> Whenever flowchart becomes complex or it spreads over more than one page, it is useful to use connectors to avoid any confusions. It is represented by a circle. "</string>
    <string name="flowline"> <b> 6. Flow lines:</b> Flow lines indicate the exact sequence in which instructions are executed. Arrows represent the direction of flow of control and relationship among different symbols of flowchart. "</string>
    <string name="rules_flow">A flowchart is a graphical representation of an algorithm. it should follow some rules while creating a flowchart \n\n<b>Rule 1:</b> Flowchart opening statement must be ‘start’ keyword. \n\n<b>Rule 2:</b> Flowchart ending statement must be ‘end’ keyword. \n\n<b>Rule 3:</b> All symbols in the flowchart must be connected with an arrow line. \n\n<b>Rule 4:</b> The decision symbol in the flowchart cannot be associated with the arrow line.</string>
    <string name="advantages_flow"><b>1.</b> Flowcharts are a better way of communicating the logic of the system. \n\n<b>2.</b> Flowcharts act as a guide for blueprint during program designed. \n\n<b>3.</b> Flowcharts help in debugging process. \n\n<b>4.</b> With the help of flowcharts programs can be easily analyzed. \n\n<b>5.</b> It provides better documentation. \n\n<b>6.</b> Flowcharts serve as a good proper documentation. \n\n<b>7.</b> Easy to trace errors in the software. \n\n<b>8.</b> Easy to understand. \n\n<b>9.</b> The flowchart can be reused for inconvenience in the future. \n\n<b>10.</b> It helps to provide correct logic.</string>
    <string name="disadvantages_flow"><b>1.</b> It is difficult to draw flowcharts for large and complex programs. \n\n<b>2.</b> There is no standard to determine the amount of detail. \n\n<b>3.</b> Difficult to reproduce the flowcharts. \n\n<b>4.</b> It is very difficult to modify the Flowchart. \n\n<b>5.</b> Making a flowchart is costly. \n\n<b>6.</b> Some developer thinks that it is waste of time. \n\n<b>7.</b> It makes software processes low. \n\n<b>8.</b> If changes are done in software, then the flowchart must be redrawn\n\n<b>Example of flowchart:</b> Draw a flowchart to input two numbers from the user and display the largest of two numbers  </string>
</resources>